<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>Granaten &#8211; GLOBAL-OFFENSIVE.COM</title>
	<atom:link href="/tag/granaten/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>/</link>
	<description>NEWS, TIPPS, TRICKS, VIDEOS, GUIDES, ANLEITUNG..</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Tue, 29 Aug 2017 10:13:45 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>de-DE</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>hourly</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>1</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=5.0.2</generator>

<image>
	<url>/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2015/08/gocom-150x150.png</url>
	<title>Granaten &#8211; GLOBAL-OFFENSIVE.COM</title>
	<link>/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>CS:GO Update &#8211; Granten Modus, neue Sticker, Waffen Balance und Radar änderungen + Video</title>
		<link>/csgo-update-granten-modus-neue-sticker-waffen-balance-und-radar-aenderungen/</link>
		<comments>/csgo-update-granten-modus-neue-sticker-waffen-balance-und-radar-aenderungen/#respond</comments>
		<pubDate>Thu, 06 Feb 2014 20:20:31 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[ESPORTS NETWORK]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[Allgemein]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Rund um CS:GO]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Updates]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[cl_cmm_showteamplayerscolor]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[CS:GO]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Granaten]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[modus]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[sticker]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[update]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[waffenmodus]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">/?p=1906</guid>
		<description><![CDATA[CS:GO Update &#8211; Granten Modus, neue Sticker, Waffen Balance und Radar änderungen Update Update Update, und schon wieder überrascht uns Valve mit einem relativ großen CS:GO Counter-Strike Global Offensive Update. Absofort werden nun während&#46;&#46;&#46;]]></description>
				<content:encoded><![CDATA[<div style="text-align: center;"><div id="esntphoenix" data-adzone="27" data-adzone-xs="6"></div></div><h3>CS:GO Update &#8211; Granten Modus, neue Sticker, Waffen Balance und Radar änderungen</h3>
<p>Update Update Update, und schon wieder überrascht uns Valve mit einem relativ großen CS:GO Counter-Strike Global Offensive Update. Absofort werden nun während des Spiels sogenannte Kapseln gedroppt, welche verschiedenste Sticker enthalten. Diese Sticker könnt ihr selbst an alle möglichen Stellen eurer Waffe &#8222;klatschen&#8220;.</p>
<p>Die Granaten besitzen nun einen zweiten Feuermodus, womit ihr diese kürzer Werfen könnt. An einigen Waffen wurde herumgeschraubt und die Waffen-Balance verändert. Eine Waffe, welche positiv verändert wurde, ist z.B. die Desert Eagle.</p>
<p>Das Radar hat interessante Änderungen erhalten und ein paar Maps wurden überarbeitet.</p>
<h3>Die neuen Sticker</h3>
<p>Absofort gibt es nun Sticker, welche ihr auf die Waffen anbringen könnt. Aus den gedroppten &#8222;Sticker Capsules&#8220; (Sticker Kapseln) können diese über einen Schlüssel für 0.75€ entpackt werden. Die Sticker könnt ihr frei auf der Waffe anbringen, ihr könnt auch 15 Sticker aufklatschen, es gibt keine Begrenzung (außer euer Portmonait ist leer).</p>
<p><a href="/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2014/02/Stickers1.png"><img class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-1907" alt="Stickers[1]" src="/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2014/02/Stickers1.png" width="1080" height="832" srcset="/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2014/02/Stickers1.png 1080w, /wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2014/02/Stickers1-300x231.png 300w, /wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2014/02/Stickers1-1024x789.png 1024w" sizes="(max-width: 1080px) 100vw, 1080px" /></a></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<h3>Granaten können nun kürzer geworfen werden:</h3>
<p>Jede Granate in Counter-Strike Global Offensive kann nun besser auf kurze Distanz geworfen werden. Wenn eine Granate gezückt wird und mit der rechten Maustaste gedrückt geworfen losgelassen wird, fliegt diese nur eine kurze Distanz. Sehr praktisch, wie wir finden.</p>
<p><a href="/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2014/02/SecondaryGrenade1.jpg"><img class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-1908" alt="SecondaryGrenade[1]" src="/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2014/02/SecondaryGrenade1.jpg" width="733" height="402" srcset="/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2014/02/SecondaryGrenade1.jpg 733w, /wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2014/02/SecondaryGrenade1-300x165.jpg 300w" sizes="(max-width: 733px) 100vw, 733px" /></a></p>
<h3>Waffen Balance wurde überarbeitet z.B. von der Deagle:</h3>
<p>Einige Waffen wurden bearbeitet bzw. optimiert. Die Desert Eagle (Deagle) benötigte in der Tat ein dringendes Improvement. Die Zielgenauigkeit erholt sich nun wesentlich schnell.</p>
<p>Deutlich mehr hat sich an der AUG und der SG 553 getan. Bei beiden Waffen wurde die Feuerrate erhöht und das Recoil, sowie die Ungenauigkeit im Zoom-Modus wurden reduziert. Das macht sie trotz des höheren Preises zu einer ernsthaften Alternative. Zudem wurde bei allen automatischen Waffen die Ungenauigkeit während dem Laufen um 50% erhöht. Das heißt man trifft mit Waffen wie der AK-47 oder der P90 während dem Laufen nicht mehr so gut. Dafür hat sich aber auch die Genauigkeit während dem Schleichen geändert. Diese wird nun anders berechnet, so dass man während dem Schleichen nun insgesamt besser trifft. Übrigens wurde auch sv_airaccelerate leicht erhöht und ist nun standardmäßig auf 12 eingestellt</p>
<h3>Teammitglieder werden nun im Radar angezeigt</h3>
<p>Jetzt heißt es nicht mehr, Paul wo bist du gerade, oder Paul bist du schon auf A-Lang? Absofort ist eindeutig erkennbar wo die Mitspieler auf dem Radar stehen. Dieses wurde durch Valve mit verschiedenen Farben, die die Spieler erhalten, deutlich gemacht. Die Funktion kann mittels cl_cmm_showteamplayerscolor 1 aktiviert werden.</p>
<p><a href="/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2014/02/Radar1.png"><img class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-1909" alt="Radar[1]" src="/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2014/02/Radar1.png" width="649" height="365" srcset="/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2014/02/Radar1.png 649w, /wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2014/02/Radar1-300x169.png 300w" sizes="(max-width: 649px) 100vw, 649px" /></a></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<h3>Die wesentlichen Änderungen direkt im Game erklärt von mrtweeday:</h3>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<h3>Weitere Änderungen</h3>
<p>Darüber hinaus wurden weitere Änderungen an Maps vorgenommen. Diese könnt ihr am besten direkt aus der folgenden Changelog entnehmen:</p>
<p>[ STICKERS ]<br />
&#8211; Added Sticker Capsules. Each capsule contains one sticker out of a series of sticker designs.<br />
&#8211; Sticker Capsules can be received as drops at the end of matches, and are opened using a Sticker Capsule Key.<br />
&#8211; A sticker can be applied to any gun, and each gun can hold multiple stickers.</p>
<p>[ MISC ]<br />
&#8211; Several adjustments to improve performance for a range of hardware configurations.<br />
&#8211; Ended Operation Bravo.<br />
&#8211; Overpass and Cobblestone maps are now available to everyone.<br />
&#8211; Removed the following items from the store:<br />
– Season’s Gifts. They are still marketable on the Community Marketplace and remain fully functional.<br />
– Operation Bravo Passes. They are still marketable on the Community Marketplace and can be redeemed for an Operation Bravo Coin.<br />
&#8211; Doing an ent_create now orients the created entity opposite the player’s orientation so it’s facing the player.<br />
&#8211; Added a new material type called ‘Lightmapped_4WayBlend’ that can be used on displacements. Documentation can be found here: https://developer.valvesoftware.com/wiki/Lightmapped_4WayBlend<br />
&#8211; Added more diagnostic information for buffer overflows in network channel.</p>
<p>[ UI ]<br />
&#8211; Removed rouge [sic] pixel on mode map selection UI.<br />
&#8211; Added player teammate colors in Competitive Mode that displays a unique color per teammate in the radar, playercount panel, scoreboard and the arrow over their head (can be toggled offline with cl_cmm_showteamplayercolors).<br />
&#8211; Reduced translucency of avatars in playercount panel and did some minor visual updates.<br />
&#8211; Enemies icons on radar are now a different shape than teammates.<br />
&#8211; Hostages on radar now have an H in the dot and never rotate.<br />
&#8211; Added sort method ‘Equipped’ to the Inventory.<br />
&#8211; Added a setting to Game Options that allows hiding Team Tags in death notices.<br />
&#8211; Team tags now scale to fit in the scoreboard and no longer overlap ping or get get cut off.<br />
&#8211; Fixed an issue where sometimes no live games could be found in the Watch panel for the first minute after game launch.</p>
<p>[ GAMEPLAY ]<br />
&#8211; All grenades now have a secondary fire that throws an underhand grenade a short distance in front of the player.<br />
– Secondary fire can be combined with primary fire to precisely adjust the strength of the throw.</p>
<p>&#8211; Weapon balance has been adjusted:<br />
– Improved Desert Eagle accuracy recovery<br />
– Improved Sg553 and AUG rates of fire.<br />
– Improved Sg553 and AUG scoped control ( reduced inaccuracy and recoil ).<br />
– Increased movement inaccuracy on all automatic weapons by 50%.<br />
– Movement inaccuracy when walking is now calculated differently, resulting in better walking accuracy across the board.<br />
&#8211; sv_airaccelerate has been slightly increased.</p>
<p>[ MAPS ]<br />
&#8211; Mirage<br />
– Fixed a bug where you could peek over a crate at CT stairs.<br />
– Added a peek position in Bombsite A connector, towards Palace exit.<br />
– Clipped benches inside palace.<br />
– Fixed some boost/exploit spots (Thanks F3RO!).<br />
– Breakable metal panels can no longer be shot through without triggering break effect.<br />
– Made it easier to get into hole leading to CT sniper window.<br />
– Made it easier to move over cart leading to B route from CT spawn.<br />
– Reworked cover in Bombsite A.<br />
– Reworked cover in Bombsite B.</p>
<p>&#8211; Overpass<br />
– Changed cover in playground.<br />
– Fixed smoke sorting on water.<br />
– Made players easier to see in park connector stairs.<br />
– Raised upper park divider to prevent peeking over it.<br />
– Increased ambient lighting.<br />
– Made bridge near Bombsite B twice as wide.<br />
– Made it easier to spot players in T side of canal.<br />
– Simplified the layout of Bombsite B slightly.<br />
– Removed small tree at CT side of upper park.<br />
– Blocked visibility through truck in Bombsite A.<br />
– Tweaked soundscape.<br />
– General optimizations.</p>
<p>&#8211; Inferno<br />
– Fixed a bug where players could get stuck in ceilingfans.<br />
– Fixed some areas where thrown C4 could get stuck.<br />
– Increased brightness slightly in hallway leading to balcony in Bombsite A.<br />
– Fixed gaps that players could see through in Bombsite B.<br />
– Made wall penetration in construction more consistent (Thanks Pawlesslol!).<br />
– Nerfed the refire rate on the churchbells (changed from infinite dings per second to 1 ding per second).<br />
– General optimizations.</p>
<p>&#8211; Dust 2<br />
– Removed dark texture near tunnel stairs.<br />
– Removed sky collision over building near T spawn.<br />
– Covered up shadow that looked like a player near CT spawn.<br />
– Fixed invisible ledges on curved corners.</p>
<p>&#8211; Assault<br />
– Fixed various graphical bugs.<br />
– Fixed bugs related to prop_physics_multiplayer.<br />
– Added a CT van to CT spawn.<br />
– Fixed an exploit where players could get out of the map.</p>
<div style="text-align: center;"><div id="esntphoenix" data-adzone="27" data-adzone-xs="6"></div></div>]]></content:encoded>
			<wfw:commentRss>/csgo-update-granten-modus-neue-sticker-waffen-balance-und-radar-aenderungen/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
		<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		</item>
		<item>
		<title>[CS:GO] Nützliche de_dust2 &#8211; Taktiken &#8211; Smokes &#8211; Flash Granaten [Tipps &#038; Tricks] [ENG]</title>
		<link>/csgo-nuetze-de_dust2-taktiken-smokes-flash-granaten-tipps-tricks-eng/</link>
		<comments>/csgo-nuetze-de_dust2-taktiken-smokes-flash-granaten-tipps-tricks-eng/#respond</comments>
		<pubDate>Sat, 18 Jan 2014 22:54:36 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[ESPORTS NETWORK]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[Allgemein]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[CS:GO Tipps & Tricks]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[de_dust2]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Granaten]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Taktik]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Video Guides]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Anleitung]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[dust2]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[smokes]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[strategie]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Tipps]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Tricks]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">/?p=1880</guid>
		<description><![CDATA[Hier mal ein paar wirklich gute Screenshots von einem Steam Community Mitglied um Granaten auf de_dust2 zu platzieren. Die Beschreibung ist auf Englisch, sollte aber für die meißten kein Problem sein. Typically if you&#8217;re&#46;&#46;&#46;]]></description>
				<content:encoded><![CDATA[<div style="text-align: center;"><div id="esntphoenix" data-adzone="27" data-adzone-xs="6"></div></div><p>Hier mal ein paar wirklich gute Screenshots von einem Steam Community Mitglied um Granaten auf de_dust2 zu platzieren. Die Beschreibung ist auf Englisch, sollte aber für die meißten kein Problem sein.</p>
<div><a href="http://i.imgur.com/bxYmfvD.jpg"><img alt="Default" src="http://i.imgur.com/bxYmfvD.jpg" /></a></div>
<div>Typically if you&#8217;re not going long immediately, you want to have a person watching doors so CTs can&#8217;t take it. If you miss your shots, there&#8217;s plenty of room and cover for you to fall back.</div>
<p><a name="tbKS3G2"></a></p>
<div id="tbKS3G2">
<div><a href="http://i.imgur.com/tbKS3G2.jpg"><img alt="" src="http://i.imgur.com/tbKS3G2.jpg" /></a></div>
<div>If you have an awp, you&#8217;re going to watch/pick mid to get the count to your teammates and damage people going by.</div>
</div>
<p><a name="bMz45xI"></a></p>
<div id="bMz45xI">
<div><a href="http://i.imgur.com/bMz45xI.jpg"><img alt="" src="http://i.imgur.com/bMz45xI.jpg" /></a></div>
<div>If they have an awp and you don&#8217;t, you can smoke mid from this spot or from b tunnels.</div>
</div>
<p><a name="cH0fdZ9"></a></p>
<div id="cH0fdZ9">
<div><a href="http://i.imgur.com/cH0fdZ9.jpg"><img alt="" src="http://i.imgur.com/cH0fdZ9.jpg" /></a></div>
<div>Have one or two players go to b tunnels and make sure it&#8217;s clear.</div>
</div>
<p><a name="5qwvdR0"></a></p>
<div id="5qwvdR0">
<div><a href="http://i.imgur.com/5qwvdR0.jpg"><img alt="" src="http://i.imgur.com/5qwvdR0.jpg" /></a></div>
<div>If you have no AWP mid, check this angle before moving out.</div>
</div>
<p><a name="Rc9RgQP"></a></p>
<div id="Rc9RgQP">
<div><a href="http://i.imgur.com/Rc9RgQP.jpg"><img alt="" src="http://i.imgur.com/Rc9RgQP.jpg" /></a></div>
<div>Once b tunnels are clear and your teammates are set up, throw this flashbang. Line it up with the wall and the balcony as shown.</div>
</div>
<p><a name="RUqA6JW"></a></p>
<div id="RUqA6JW">
<div><a href="http://i.imgur.com/RUqA6JW.jpg"><img alt="" src="http://i.imgur.com/RUqA6JW.jpg" /></a></div>
<div>The flash should pop right about here. There&#8217;s almost no reaction time for somebody watching cat.</div>
</div>
<p><a name="AQtPkn1"></a></p>
<div id="AQtPkn1">
<div><a href="http://i.imgur.com/AQtPkn1.jpg"><img alt="" src="http://i.imgur.com/AQtPkn1.jpg" /></a></div>
<div>While the B guy is clearing things out and getting ready, move up cat, keeping your crosshair at mid until you come to the last support bricks on the wall to your right.</div>
</div>
<p><a name="zJZOtv7"></a></p>
<div id="zJZOtv7">
<div><a href="http://i.imgur.com/zJZOtv7.jpg"><img alt="" src="http://i.imgur.com/zJZOtv7.jpg" /></a></div>
</div>
<p><a name="4oRxgPR"></a></p>
<div id="4oRxgPR">
<div><a href="http://i.imgur.com/4oRxgPR.jpg"><img alt="" src="http://i.imgur.com/4oRxgPR.jpg" /></a></div>
<div>I like to prefire this corner.</div>
</div>
<p><a name="p6aDv5d"></a></p>
<div id="p6aDv5d">
<div><a href="http://i.imgur.com/p6aDv5d.jpg"><img alt="" src="http://i.imgur.com/p6aDv5d.jpg" /></a></div>
<div>Once inner cat is clear, take position here and wait for your teammate to tell you he&#8217;s flashing.</div>
</div>
<p><a name="pX81sKh"></a></p>
<div id="pX81sKh">
<div><a href="http://i.imgur.com/pX81sKh.jpg"><img alt="" src="http://i.imgur.com/pX81sKh.jpg" /></a></div>
<div>Throw a flashbang here when the other flash is about there for maximum effectiveness.</div>
</div>
<p><a name="9SSJAjo"></a></p>
<div id="9SSJAjo">
<div><a href="http://i.imgur.com/9SSJAjo.jpg"><img alt="" src="http://i.imgur.com/9SSJAjo.jpg" /></a></div>
<div>Move up and prefire this angle.</div>
</div>
<p><a name="vqvk2JZ"></a></p>
<div id="vqvk2JZ">
<div><a href="http://i.imgur.com/vqvk2JZ.jpg"><img alt="" src="http://i.imgur.com/vqvk2JZ.jpg" /></a></div>
<div>You can throw a running flashbang here.</div>
</div>
<p><a name="6eVncvx"></a></p>
<div id="6eVncvx">
<div><a href="http://i.imgur.com/6eVncvx.jpg"><img alt="" src="http://i.imgur.com/6eVncvx.jpg" /></a></div>
<div>It pops about there.</div>
</div>
<p><a name="GThvS78"></a></p>
<div id="GThvS78">
<div><a href="http://i.imgur.com/GThvS78.jpg"><img alt="" src="http://i.imgur.com/GThvS78.jpg" /></a></div>
<div>Once A is clear / being cleared and you need people to cross, you can smoke CT. Go to this corner&#8230;</div>
</div>
<p><a name="10FUE97"></a></p>
<div id="10FUE97">
<div><a href="http://i.imgur.com/10FUE97.jpg"><img alt="" src="http://i.imgur.com/10FUE97.jpg" /></a></div>
<div>Line up your crosshair with the top right corner of the door, and throw.</div>
</div>
<p><a name="CtbpegC"></a></p>
<div id="CtbpegC">
<div><a href="http://i.imgur.com/CtbpegC.jpg"><img alt="" src="http://i.imgur.com/CtbpegC.jpg" /></a></div>
<div>The smoke will cover all sight from CT / mid.</div>
</div>
<p><a name="tH5dzF5"></a></p>
<div id="tH5dzF5">
<div><a href="http://i.imgur.com/tH5dzF5.jpg"><img alt="" src="http://i.imgur.com/tH5dzF5.jpg" /></a></div>
<div>When moving through A, this is a popular flashbang.</div>
</div>
<p><a name="2a0tnvh"></a></p>
<div id="2a0tnvh">
<div><a href="http://i.imgur.com/2a0tnvh.jpg"><img alt="" src="http://i.imgur.com/2a0tnvh.jpg" /></a></div>
<div>Run and jump off of the bleach container on the ground.</div>
</div>
<p><a name="M8LP8lt"></a></p>
<div id="M8LP8lt">
<div><a href="http://i.imgur.com/M8LP8lt.jpg"><img alt="" src="http://i.imgur.com/M8LP8lt.jpg" /></a></div>
<div>The flash should pop around here, blinding players at car or who are playing the corner loosely.</div>
</div>
<p><a name="VEx6imX"></a></p>
<div id="VEx6imX">
<div><a href="http://i.imgur.com/VEx6imX.jpg"><img alt="" src="http://i.imgur.com/VEx6imX.jpg" /></a></div>
<div>After clearing outside doors, you may want to throw this flash to blind people at barrels. The flash is nearly impossible to see coming, blinds for a full second, and there&#8217;s a non-solid object blocking their view of it, so they can&#8217;t see it but still get flashed.</div>
</div>
<p><a name="p47FDU2"></a></p>
<div id="p47FDU2">
<div><a href="http://i.imgur.com/p47FDU2.jpg"><img alt="" src="http://i.imgur.com/p47FDU2.jpg" /></a></div>
<div>Peek with the flash.</div>
</div>
<p><a name="GLdhUTQ"></a></p>
<div id="GLdhUTQ">
<div><a href="http://i.imgur.com/GLdhUTQ.jpg"><img alt="" src="http://i.imgur.com/GLdhUTQ.jpg" /></a></div>
</div>
<p><a name="6M19B3l"></a></p>
<div id="6M19B3l">
<div><a href="http://i.imgur.com/6M19B3l.jpg"><img alt="" src="http://i.imgur.com/6M19B3l.jpg" /></a></div>
<div>Check pit.</div>
</div>
<p><a name="OFUYh2F"></a></p>
<div id="OFUYh2F">
<div><a href="http://i.imgur.com/OFUYh2F.jpg"><img alt="" src="http://i.imgur.com/OFUYh2F.jpg" /></a></div>
<div>Take A as normal.</div>
</div>
<p><a name="qJhAyXn"></a></p>
<div id="qJhAyXn">
<div><a href="http://i.imgur.com/qJhAyXn.jpg"><img alt="" src="http://i.imgur.com/qJhAyXn.jpg" /></a></div>
<div>This is a good spot for playing cat.</div>
</div>
<p><a name="jGhJo1T"></a></p>
<div id="jGhJo1T">
<div><a href="http://i.imgur.com/jGhJo1T.jpg"><img alt="" src="http://i.imgur.com/jGhJo1T.jpg" /></a></div>
<div>If overrun, you can drop down for a second shot.</div>
</div>
<p><a name="NuNcRJo"></a></p>
<div id="NuNcRJo">
<div><a href="http://i.imgur.com/NuNcRJo.jpg"><img alt="" src="http://i.imgur.com/NuNcRJo.jpg" /></a></div>
<div>This is a nice spot to awp from.</div>
</div>
<p><a name="OXys167"></a></p>
<div id="OXys167">
<div><a href="http://i.imgur.com/OXys167.jpg"><img alt="" src="http://i.imgur.com/OXys167.jpg" /></a></div>
<div>This too. Be aware that the box you&#8217;re behind is spammable.</div>
</div>
<p><a name="eDSwZtb"></a></p>
<div id="eDSwZtb">
<div><a href="http://i.imgur.com/eDSwZtb.jpg"><img alt="" src="http://i.imgur.com/eDSwZtb.jpg" /></a></div>
<div>This is a good spot too. Just kidding.</div>
</div>
<p><a name="4MFmAn9"></a></p>
<div id="4MFmAn9">
<div><a href="http://i.imgur.com/4MFmAn9.jpg"><img alt="" src="http://i.imgur.com/4MFmAn9.jpg" /></a></div>
<div>For going mid-b, you can smoke and/or spam through A doors.</div>
</div>
<p><a name="zPi0gN9"></a></p>
<div id="zPi0gN9">
<div><a href="http://i.imgur.com/zPi0gN9.jpg"><img alt="" src="http://i.imgur.com/zPi0gN9.jpg" /></a></div>
<div>Line up in this corner.</div>
</div>
<p><a name="4T6GnTY"></a></p>
<div id="4T6GnTY">
<div><a href="http://i.imgur.com/4T6GnTY.jpg"><img alt="" src="http://i.imgur.com/4T6GnTY.jpg" /></a></div>
<div>Put your crosshair at the little nub on the wall and throw.</div>
</div>
<p><a name="OpDyNrX"></a></p>
<div id="OpDyNrX">
<div><a href="http://i.imgur.com/OpDyNrX.jpg"><img alt="" src="http://i.imgur.com/OpDyNrX.jpg" /></a></div>
<div>It pops about here.</div>
</div>
<p><a name="l2zVOGy"></a></p>
<div id="l2zVOGy">
<div><a href="http://i.imgur.com/l2zVOGy.jpg"><img alt="" src="http://i.imgur.com/l2zVOGy.jpg" /></a></div>
<div>This will fully blind anybody watching from CT or doors.</div>
</div>
<p><a name="isVQzHr"></a></p>
<div id="isVQzHr">
<div><a href="http://i.imgur.com/isVQzHr.jpg"><img alt="" src="http://i.imgur.com/isVQzHr.jpg" /></a></div>
<div>Place your crosshair on the arrow on the box in CT and throw a smoke.</div>
</div>
<p><a name="Sizqo2v"></a></p>
<div id="Sizqo2v">
<div><a href="http://i.imgur.com/Sizqo2v.jpg"><img alt="" src="http://i.imgur.com/Sizqo2v.jpg" /></a></div>
<div>This will completely smoke off CT.</div>
</div>
<p><a name="dJpgrCW"></a></p>
<div id="dJpgrCW">
<div><a href="http://i.imgur.com/dJpgrCW.jpg"><img alt="" src="http://i.imgur.com/dJpgrCW.jpg" /></a></div>
<div>This is a useful entry/retake flash.</div>
</div>
<p><a name="I7pNZLL"></a></p>
<div id="I7pNZLL">
<div><a href="http://i.imgur.com/I7pNZLL.jpg"><img alt="" src="http://i.imgur.com/I7pNZLL.jpg" /></a></div>
<div>It pops about here.</div>
</div>
<p><a name="x3x7TH6"></a></p>
<div id="x3x7TH6">
<div><a href="http://i.imgur.com/x3x7TH6.jpg"><img alt="" src="http://i.imgur.com/x3x7TH6.jpg" /></a></div>
<div>Coordinate this flash with the previous one and the whole site will be blind.</div>
</div>
<p><a name="GWd5cbd"></a></p>
<div id="GWd5cbd">
<div><a href="http://i.imgur.com/GWd5cbd.jpg"><img alt="" src="http://i.imgur.com/GWd5cbd.jpg" /></a></div>
<div>That flash pops here.</div>
</div>
<p><a name="kXdswyG"></a></p>
<div id="kXdswyG">
<h2>CT setups</h2>
<div><a href="http://i.imgur.com/kXdswyG.jpg"><img alt="CT setups" src="http://i.imgur.com/kXdswyG.jpg" /></a></div>
<div>When going long, don&#8217;t run forwards. You can get blinded by the deep flashes people like to throw.</div>
</div>
<p><a name="YU7IDFZ"></a></p>
<div id="YU7IDFZ">
<div><a href="http://i.imgur.com/YU7IDFZ.jpg"><img alt="" src="http://i.imgur.com/YU7IDFZ.jpg" /></a></div>
<div>When you see this pipe, stop, and pull out your primary. This keeps you in cover and lets you snap around to watch doors.</div>
</div>
<p><a name="kmPD2tL"></a></p>
<div id="kmPD2tL">
<div><a href="http://i.imgur.com/kmPD2tL.jpg"><img alt="" src="http://i.imgur.com/kmPD2tL.jpg" /></a></div>
</div>
<p><a name="Sg5tnaD"></a></p>
<div id="Sg5tnaD">
<div><a href="http://i.imgur.com/Sg5tnaD.jpg"><img alt="" src="http://i.imgur.com/Sg5tnaD.jpg" /></a></div>
<div>To prevent an A push, you can have a teammate throw this flash.</div>
</div>
<p><a name="D1DKZBy"></a></p>
<div id="D1DKZBy">
<div><a href="http://i.imgur.com/D1DKZBy.jpg"><img alt="" src="http://i.imgur.com/D1DKZBy.jpg" /></a></div>
</div>
<p><a name="LuZytBo"></a></p>
<div id="LuZytBo">
<div><a href="http://i.imgur.com/LuZytBo.jpg"><img alt="" src="http://i.imgur.com/LuZytBo.jpg" /></a></div>
<div>It pops here.</div>
</div>
<p><a name="9tgx5J3"></a></p>
<div id="9tgx5J3">
<div><a href="http://i.imgur.com/9tgx5J3.jpg"><img alt="" src="http://i.imgur.com/9tgx5J3.jpg" /></a></div>
<div>Anybody coming through A doors will be blind.</div>
</div>
<p><a name="HDUU19k"></a></p>
<div id="HDUU19k">
<div><a href="http://i.imgur.com/HDUU19k.jpg"><img alt="" src="http://i.imgur.com/HDUU19k.jpg" /></a></div>
<div>They&#8217;ll also block their teammates while blind.</div>
</div>
<p><a name="fOdpseA"></a></p>
<div id="fOdpseA">
<div><a href="http://i.imgur.com/fOdpseA.jpg"><img alt="" src="http://i.imgur.com/fOdpseA.jpg" /></a></div>
<div>Smoke off A for 15 seconds of safety.</div>
</div>
<p><a name="CIt0Uju"></a></p>
<div id="CIt0Uju">
<div><a href="http://i.imgur.com/CIt0Uju.jpg"><img alt="" src="http://i.imgur.com/CIt0Uju.jpg" /></a></div>
<div>Get in position.</div>
</div>
<p><a name="kDcmXvP"></a></p>
<div id="kDcmXvP">
<div><a href="http://i.imgur.com/kDcmXvP.jpg"><img alt="" src="http://i.imgur.com/kDcmXvP.jpg" /></a></div>
</div>
<p><a name="nBX6TIP"></a></p>
<div id="nBX6TIP">
<div><a href="http://i.imgur.com/nBX6TIP.jpg"><img alt="" src="http://i.imgur.com/nBX6TIP.jpg" /></a></div>
<div>Watching A doors like this lets you see people coming easily and provides good cover to fall back on.</div>
</div>
<p><a name="1UH4lcY"></a></p>
<div id="1UH4lcY">
<div><a href="http://i.imgur.com/1UH4lcY.jpg"><img alt="" src="http://i.imgur.com/1UH4lcY.jpg" /></a></div>
<div>You can see people&#8217;s shadows coming in.</div>
</div>
<p><a name="JL8XmtJ"></a></p>
<div id="JL8XmtJ">
<div><a href="http://i.imgur.com/JL8XmtJ.jpg"><img alt="" src="http://i.imgur.com/JL8XmtJ.jpg" /></a></div>
<div>Boost here to screw up your opponent&#8217;s angles.</div>
</div>
<p><a name="AozBcCk"></a></p>
<div id="AozBcCk">
<h2>B site</h2>
<div><a href="http://i.imgur.com/AozBcCk.jpg"><img alt="B site" src="http://i.imgur.com/AozBcCk.jpg" /></a></div>
<div>This angle lets you see people coming in, even if they are walking.</div>
</div>
<p><a name="f8W9cuS"></a></p>
<div id="f8W9cuS">
<div><a href="http://i.imgur.com/f8W9cuS.jpg"><img alt="" src="http://i.imgur.com/f8W9cuS.jpg" /></a></div>
<div>You can have one person on the boxes and one person watching mid.</div>
</div>
<p><a name="QkZi26O"></a></p>
<div id="QkZi26O">
<div><a href="http://i.imgur.com/QkZi26O.jpg"><img alt="" src="http://i.imgur.com/QkZi26O.jpg" /></a></div>
<div>Stopping a B tunnels push is a few steps and a turn away.</div>
</div>
<p><a name="L0oJmFg"></a></p>
<div id="L0oJmFg">
<div><a href="http://i.imgur.com/L0oJmFg.jpg"><img alt="" src="http://i.imgur.com/L0oJmFg.jpg" /></a></div>
<div>Jumping here with a MAG-7 / Nova / P90 can be surprising and damaging.</div>
</div>
<p><a name="6A9js6B"></a></p>
<div id="6A9js6B">
<div><a href="http://i.imgur.com/6A9js6B.jpg"><img alt="" src="http://i.imgur.com/6A9js6B.jpg" /></a></div>
<div>To smoke mid against an AWPer from CT, go into this corner here</div>
</div>
<p><a name="1WvlJyn"></a></p>
<div id="1WvlJyn">
<div><a href="http://i.imgur.com/1WvlJyn.jpg"><img alt="" src="http://i.imgur.com/1WvlJyn.jpg" /></a></div>
<div>Throw the smoke at the bottom right corner of the window.</div>
</div>
<p><a name="yphAV1K"></a></p>
<div id="yphAV1K">
<div><a href="http://i.imgur.com/yphAV1K.jpg"><img alt="" src="http://i.imgur.com/yphAV1K.jpg" /></a></div>
</div>
<p><a name="mXyZOKf"></a></p>
<div id="mXyZOKf">
<div><a href="http://i.imgur.com/mXyZOKf.jpg"><img alt="" src="http://i.imgur.com/mXyZOKf.jpg" /></a></div>
<div>Here&#8217;s a useful counterflash for playing boxes/b ramp.</div>
</div>
<p><a name="gPZ3e7s"></a></p>
<div id="gPZ3e7s">
<div><a href="http://i.imgur.com/gPZ3e7s.jpg"><img alt="" src="http://i.imgur.com/gPZ3e7s.jpg" /></a></div>
<div>Another counterflash for pit &#8211; stand between these two green dots about 1/3 of the way down the pit.</div>
</div>
<p><a name="oTovGz6"></a></p>
<div id="oTovGz6">
<div><a href="http://i.imgur.com/oTovGz6.jpg"><img alt="" src="http://i.imgur.com/oTovGz6.jpg" /></a></div>
<div>Aim at this green dot.</div>
</div>
<p><a name="wE4LRmD"></a></p>
<div id="wE4LRmD">
<div><a href="http://i.imgur.com/wE4LRmD.jpg"><img alt="" src="http://i.imgur.com/wE4LRmD.jpg" /></a></div>
<div>The flash will pop as soon as the terrorists can see it and fully blind them.</div>
</div>
<p><a name="xEXxVQp"></a></p>
<div id="xEXxVQp">
<div><a href="http://i.imgur.com/xEXxVQp.jpg"><img alt="" src="http://i.imgur.com/xEXxVQp.jpg" /></a></div>
<div>Another flash if you hear them coming through tunnels.</div>
</div>
<p><a name="c0XDSKg"></a></p>
<div id="c0XDSKg">
<div><a href="http://i.imgur.com/c0XDSKg.jpg"><img alt="" src="http://i.imgur.com/c0XDSKg.jpg" /></a></div>
<div>Throw a flashbang here to slow a mid-b push.</div>
</div>
<p><a name="8mfcu6a"></a></p>
<div id="8mfcu6a">
<div><a href="http://i.imgur.com/8mfcu6a.jpg"><img alt="" src="http://i.imgur.com/8mfcu6a.jpg" /></a></div>
<div>It pops here.</div>
</div>
<p><a name="8bmx1Yq"></a></p>
<div id="8bmx1Yq">
<div><a href="http://i.imgur.com/8bmx1Yq.jpg"><img alt="" src="http://i.imgur.com/8bmx1Yq.jpg" /></a></div>
<div>Throwing a flash here will blind anybody ramp/goose/barrels.</div>
</div>
<p><a name="qdOXTIS"></a></p>
<div id="qdOXTIS">
<h2>It lands somewhere around the site.</h2>
<div><a href="http://i.imgur.com/qdOXTIS.jpg"><img alt="It lands somewhere around the site." src="http://i.imgur.com/qdOXTIS.jpg" /></a></div>
</div>
<p><a name="F75xkrU"></a></p>
<div id="F75xkrU">
<div><a href="http://i.imgur.com/F75xkrU.jpg"><img alt="" src="http://i.imgur.com/F75xkrU.jpg" /></a></div>
</div>
<p><a name="9rJOeAT"></a></p>
<div id="9rJOeAT">
<div><a href="http://i.imgur.com/9rJOeAT.jpg"><img alt="" src="http://i.imgur.com/9rJOeAT.jpg" /></a></div>
<div>This is a good spot to get exit frags from B and save a weapon.</div>
</div>
<p><a name="TTkJYQj"></a></p>
<div id="TTkJYQj">
<div><a href="http://i.imgur.com/TTkJYQj.jpg"><img alt="" src="http://i.imgur.com/TTkJYQj.jpg" /></a></div>
<div>This too.</div>
</div>
<p><a name="NYYoLNQ"></a></p>
<div id="NYYoLNQ">
<div><a href="http://i.imgur.com/NYYoLNQ.jpg"><img alt="" src="http://i.imgur.com/NYYoLNQ.jpg" /></a></div>
</div>
<div style="text-align: center;"><div id="esntphoenix" data-adzone="27" data-adzone-xs="6"></div></div>]]></content:encoded>
			<wfw:commentRss>/csgo-nuetze-de_dust2-taktiken-smokes-flash-granaten-tipps-tricks-eng/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
		<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		</item>
		<item>
		<title>CS: GO Update: Granaten fliegen wieder durch Scheiben und Schächte!</title>
		<link>/cs-go-update-granaten-fliegen-wieder-durch-scheiben-und-schachte/</link>
		<comments>/cs-go-update-granaten-fliegen-wieder-durch-scheiben-und-schachte/#respond</comments>
		<pubDate>Fri, 10 May 2013 19:44:03 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[ESPORTS NETWORK]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[Allgemein]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Rund um CS:GO]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Updates]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[fenster]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Granaten]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[hotfix]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[schacht]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[smoke]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">/?p=1468</guid>
		<description><![CDATA[Vor wenigen Minuten wurde ein kleines aber wichtiges Hotfix herausgebracht. Seit dem letzten Update war es nicht mehr möglich mit Granaten die zerstörbaren Scheiben und Schächte einzuwerfen stattdessen prallten diese am Fenster ab. Darüber&#46;&#46;&#46;]]></description>
				<content:encoded><![CDATA[<div style="text-align: center;"><div id="esntphoenix" data-adzone="27" data-adzone-xs="6"></div></div><p>Vor wenigen Minuten wurde ein kleines aber wichtiges Hotfix herausgebracht. Seit dem letzten Update war es nicht mehr möglich mit Granaten die zerstörbaren Scheiben und Schächte einzuwerfen stattdessen prallten diese am Fenster ab. Darüber hinaus wurde der Exploit behoben, dass die CTs nicht mehr die Möglichkeit haben die  Geiseln durch dünne Böden hindurch aufzunehmen.</p>
<blockquote>
<p>Release Notes for 5/10/2013</p>
<p>[ MISC ]</p>
<p>&#8211; Fixed an exploit of CTs boosting and picking up hostages through thin floors.<br />&#8211; Restored proper grenade interaction with breakable surfaces.</p>
</blockquote>
<div style="text-align: center;"><div id="esntphoenix" data-adzone="27" data-adzone-xs="6"></div></div>]]></content:encoded>
			<wfw:commentRss>/cs-go-update-granaten-fliegen-wieder-durch-scheiben-und-schachte/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
		<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		</item>
		<item>
		<title>Die &#8222;neuen&#8220; Waffennamen</title>
		<link>/die-neuen-waffennamen/</link>
		<comments>/die-neuen-waffennamen/#comments</comments>
		<pubDate>Sat, 13 Oct 2012 15:09:30 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[ESPORTS NETWORK]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[Allgemein]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[CS:GO Tipps & Tricks]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Die Config]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Rund um CS:GO]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sonstiges]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Buyscript]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Config]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Config.cfg]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Granaten]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Script]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[waffen]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Waffenname]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">/?p=234</guid>
		<description><![CDATA[Hier eine Liste der &#8222;neuen&#8220; Waffennamen und deren Name in der Config. (Wichtig für das Buyscript) &#160; Pistolen: Name Name in der Config Glock-18 &#8222;glock&#8220; P2000 (CT) &#8222;hkp2000&#8220; Tec-9 (T) &#8222;tec9&#8220; P250 &#8222;p250&#8220; Desert&#46;&#46;&#46;]]></description>
				<content:encoded><![CDATA[<div style="text-align: center;"><div id="esntphoenix" data-adzone="27" data-adzone-xs="6"></div></div><p>Hier eine Liste der &#8222;neuen&#8220; Waffennamen und deren Name in der Config. (Wichtig für das Buyscript)<span id="more-234"></span></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><span style="text-decoration: underline">Pistolen:</span></p>
<table border="1">
<tbody>
<tr>
<th>Name</th>
<th>Name in der Config</th>
</tr>
<tr>
<td width="200">Glock-18</td>
<td>&#8222;glock&#8220;</td>
</tr>
<tr>
<td>P2000 (CT)</td>
<td>&#8222;hkp2000&#8220;</td>
</tr>
<tr>
<td>Tec-9 (T)</td>
<td>&#8222;tec9&#8220;</td>
</tr>
<tr>
<td>P250</td>
<td>&#8222;p250&#8220;</td>
</tr>
<tr>
<td>Desert Eagle</td>
<td>&#8222;deagle&#8220;</td>
</tr>
<tr>
<td>Dual Berettas</td>
<td>&#8222;elites&#8220;</td>
</tr>
<tr>
<td>Five-Seven</td>
<td>&#8222;fiveseven&#8220;</td>
</tr>
</tbody>
</table>
<p><span style="text-decoration: underline">Shotguns:</span></p>
<table border="1">
<tbody>
<tr>
<th>Name</th>
<th>Name in der Config</th>
</tr>
<tr>
<td width="200">Nova</td>
<td>“nova”</td>
</tr>
<tr>
<td>Abgesägte Schrotflinte (T)</td>
<td>“sawedoff”</td>
</tr>
<tr>
<td>MAG-7 (CT)</td>
<td>“mag7″</td>
</tr>
<tr>
<td>XM1014</td>
<td>“xm1014″</td>
</tr>
</tbody>
</table>
<p><span style="text-decoration: underline">Sub Machine Guns:</span></p>
<table border="1">
<tbody>
<tr>
<th>Name</th>
<th>Name in der Config</th>
</tr>
<tr>
<td width="200">Mac-10 (T)</td>
<td>“mac10″</td>
</tr>
<tr>
<td>MP9 (CT)</td>
<td>“mp9&#8243;</td>
</tr>
<tr>
<td>MAG-7 (CT)</td>
<td>“mag7″</td>
</tr>
<tr>
<td>PP-Bizon</td>
<td>“bizon”</td>
</tr>
<tr>
<td>UMP-45</td>
<td>&#8222;ump45&#8220;</td>
</tr>
<tr>
<td>MP7</td>
<td>&#8222;mp7&#8220;</td>
</tr>
<tr>
<td>P90</td>
<td>&#8222;p90&#8220;</td>
</tr>
</tbody>
</table>
<p><span style="text-decoration: underline">Rifles:</span></p>
<table border="1">
<tbody>
<tr>
<th>Name</th>
<th>Name in der Config</th>
</tr>
<tr>
<td width="200">Galil AR (T)</td>
<td>“galilar”</td>
</tr>
<tr>
<td>AK-47 (T)</td>
<td>“ak47″</td>
</tr>
<tr>
<td>FAMAS (CT)</td>
<td>“famas”</td>
</tr>
<tr>
<td>M4A1 (CT)</td>
<td>“m4a1″</td>
</tr>
<tr>
<td>AUG (CT)</td>
<td>&#8222;aug”</td>
</tr>
<tr>
<td>SG 556 (T)</td>
<td>&#8222;sg556″</td>
</tr>
<tr>
<td>SSG 08</td>
<td>“ssg08″</td>
</tr>
<tr>
<td>AWP</td>
<td>&#8222;awp&#8220;</td>
</tr>
<tr>
<td>G3SG1 (T)</td>
<td>“g3sg1″</td>
</tr>
<tr>
<td>SCAR-20 (CT)</td>
<td>“scar20″</td>
</tr>
</tbody>
</table>
<p><span style="text-decoration: underline">Machine Guns:</span></p>
<table border="1">
<tbody>
<tr>
<th>Name</th>
<th>Name in der Config</th>
</tr>
<tr>
<td width="200">M249</td>
<td>“m249″</td>
</tr>
<tr>
<td>Negev</td>
<td>“negev”</td>
</tr>
</tbody>
</table>
<p><span style="text-decoration: underline">Equipment:</span></p>
<table border="1">
<tbody>
<tr>
<th>Name</th>
<th>Name in der Config</th>
</tr>
<tr>
<td width="200">Kevlar-West</td>
<td>“vest”</td>
</tr>
<tr>
<td>Kevlar-West + Helm</td>
<td>“vesthelm”</td>
</tr>
<tr>
<td>Defuse-Kit</td>
<td>“defuser”</td>
</tr>
<tr>
<td>Zeus x27</td>
<td>“taser”</td>
</tr>
</tbody>
</table>
<p><span style="text-decoration: underline">Granaten:</span></p>
<table border="1">
<tbody>
<tr>
<th>Name</th>
<th>Name in der Config</th>
</tr>
<tr>
<td width="200">Flashbang</td>
<td>“flashbang”</td>
</tr>
<tr>
<td>High Explosive Grenade</td>
<td>“hegrenade”</td>
</tr>
<tr>
<td>Smoke Grenade</td>
<td>“smokegrenade”</td>
</tr>
<tr>
<td>Decoy Grenade</td>
<td>“decoy”</td>
</tr>
<tr>
<td>Molotov</td>
<td>“molotov”</td>
</tr>
<tr>
<td>Fire Grenade</td>
<td>“incgrenade”</td>
</tr>
</tbody>
</table>
<div style="text-align: center;"><div id="esntphoenix" data-adzone="27" data-adzone-xs="6"></div></div>]]></content:encoded>
			<wfw:commentRss>/die-neuen-waffennamen/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
		<slash:comments>4</slash:comments>
		</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
